Since ancient times, the Sirius have chosen a member of their royal family by oracle
and revered them as an agent of God.
As a mark of kingship,
they were permitted to possess the Ark that could exert its
power over all things, which the Sirius claimed was a gift from God.
That is what they called the Ark of Sirius.
So this is the tomb of that royal family?
Yes.
It doesn't look like this place was ransacked.
Do you think the vampires didn't notice it?
When they didn't find the Ark upstairs,
they probably assumed that this was just a tomb.
But if my interpretation of the ancient text is correct...
Professor?
What's this place?
A shrine made in the style of the original holy grounds.
Something like a auxiliary holy ground, perhaps.
Holy ground?
The place said to be the origin of the Sirius and the place where the Ark was born.
It's also the only place where the Ark can be sealed.
So then the real holy ground is...
In South Karafuto, most likely.
For some unknown reason, the Sirius had to leave their homeland in the distant past.
They supposedly forged a treasure that would facilitate the
move from the holy grounds—a counterpart to the Ark.
This is a secret shrine made to hold that treasure.
That treasure, known only to the keepers of the Ark
who forged it and their true heirs, is here somewhere.
"This vessel was created by means unknown to us."
"By its power, the Divine Ark may be suppressed and sent away."
This is it.
If the seal on the Ark in the true holy grounds is undone,
I believe that Yuliy will have need of this.
Get ready to leave!
All right!
Let's hurry.
And here I was thinking I'd be able to get home to London.
We're heading to where Yuliy is!
If I'm to live
by inertia
There's probably nothing
wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
Oooh, I've been waiting for you!
I've been waiting so, so long!
The hell are those?
Are they vampires or what?
Let me just go ahead and introduce myself!
My name is Klarwein!
The masses, mistaking the fruits of my labor for magic, have taken to calling me the Wizard,
but I am nothing other than an ultra-genius scientist!
Scientist?
You're telling me you made vampires into these robot things?
Precisely!
The trial run with a human worked, so this time I mass-produced them using vampires!
Aren't they wonderful?
Now, it's time for the live-combat testing I've been so looking forward to!
We've found more infected?
Yeah. Just a few, though.
They're being quarantined on the lowest deck.
Everyone's too afraid of getting infected to get near them.
Yuliy!
How do you like my little honey bunnys?
You know, if I didn't give these bodies such a drastic makeover, they'd have died long ago!
Have I caught your interest?
Then I'll explain, you ignorant, uneducated fools!
Our vampire friends are suffering from a fatal disease right now!
Nobody understands the where or why of the source!
They're so worried about when they'll be infected with the
mysterious disease that they can't even get a good night's sleep!
Oh, wait!
They're vampires, so they'd be sleeping during the day!
Yo.
A fatal disease?
For vampires?
Indeed!
Their inability to cure it drove them to beg for my assistance with tears in their eyes!
But since the moment that Lord Yevgraf found the Ark of Sirius,
he's refused to even acknowledge the existence of my wonderful project!
Don't you think that's awful?
He thinks that he'll be able to cure the disease with the power of the Ark!
Even though we don't even have a clear idea of what it is!
What a foolish, unscientific way to think!
It would be better for it to stay sealed for all eternity!
That way the vampires would realize just how wonderful my inventions are,
What the hell is he on about?
and beg me to help them again!
Bishop.
So, for the sake of having Lord Yevgraf understand the value of my sweethearts, please die!
What are you doing? What are you doing!
Hold still for a second!
What are you, a puppy?
And another!
Bishop!
W-Wait a minute!
My super-genius inventions are going to be lost to time because of a stupid thing like this?
I-I won't accept it!
I can't accept this!
That was close!
You're crazy, you know?
I didn't think you'd have any problems dodging it.
Are you picking a fight?
That disease he was talking about...
I need to know more.
Same here.
A fatal disease that only vampires get,
and one so bad that they need to rely on a mysterious, borderline-occult power to cure it.
Pretty pathetic, if you ask me.
Let's hurry.
Tamara, is the Ark of Sirius still sleeping?
We'll wake it up soon!
Right, Lord Yev?
Yes, we will.
What is it?
The men we quarantined have died.
They didn't ashify. Their bodies are still intact.
I see.
Take care when disposing of the corpses.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Larissa?
Are we gonna die like that too when we get sick?
I sure hope not! I don't want to die like a human!
Right, Lord—
I'd like to be by myself for a bit.
It's been a thousand years since the blood pact freed me from humanity's irksome yoke.
I became an immortal vampire, and ruled for a time that had no end.
It was truly a blessed time for me.
And this is how it ends?
Is our blood really this fragile?
Are we no different from our livestock,
those foolish humans?
Should I just accept that as fate,
as the senile old men say?
No!
I will keep fighting!
Even if I become the last vampire,
even if I must use the power of the inferior Sirius!
With my hands, with my own
noble blood, I will change this fate!
Is that it?
That's where the Ark of Sirius
and Dad are!
I like it.
This is just screaming "Ahead lies the Ark," isn't it?
This place feels eerie as all hell!
Well, aren't you eager?
Hey, what happened?
Dad...
Are you telling me to stay away?
Yuliy!
Are you all right?
I didn't know anything.
Nothing about Dad,
nothing about my race.
So as the last remnant of the Sirius,
I need to know everything.
Don't you agree, Dad?
Yuliy!
Mom...
Dad...
Dad!
I'll protect Yuliy and Mom!
This is a really nice place.
I almost feel like I'm back in my homeland.
You saved my sons' lives.
If you don't have anywhere better to go,
then you can stay here forever if you like.
I appreciate it, but...
Alexei.
I still have business that I need to take care of.
The Ark of Sirius?
That's right.
I have secret orders to find and appropriate it.
I was having no luck, but...
By pure chance, I found you.
I'm sorry that I didn't tell you before.
I didn't mean to deceive you.
What will you do now?
I don't know.
I've grown so fond of Dogville, and if I steal the ark, I'll be breaking the peace here.
Akasaka...
But remember this.
Every major power, not just Japan,
is secretly searching for the Ark.
It's only a matter of time before they reach this village.
Alexei,
when that happens, will you be able to protect your Ark?
But why?
He was completely open with us!
Why does Akasaka have to be—
Any who learn of the Ark, and any who wish to take the Ark, must be buried along with their knowledge.
This is one of our most ancient laws.
So that the royal family that protects the Ark may have a peaceful rest,
their followers have enforced that law for generations.
I do not wish for that man's death either.
I understand that the Ark is important to our people.
But can any object be so important that we have to sacrifice outsiders' lives to protect it?
Even if we kill Akasaka, someone else will come.
Are we going to do such a fruitless thing every time that happens?
No matter what hardships befall us, the Sirius will live here with the Ark.
That is the pride of the Sirius.
Our pride?
You're telling me that killing God-knows-how-many people for the Ark will be our pride?
The village accepted Sachi—accepted a human into their ranks as my wife.
You yourself were the one who affirmed that decision!
We will co-exist with humans.
Isn't that our new pride?
Why are you trying to do something that would destroy that?
Gustav.
I want to seal the Ark of Sirius away.
I want to put an end to this.
The Sirius need to break away from our old conventions.
I think that would be what's best for our future.
So Gustav,
teach me how to seal the Ark!
I'm not sure if...
Please!
It's our only option!
Gustav...
Take it to Karafuto.
That is the place of the Sirius' birth,
and the holy land where the Ark came into being.
It may be possible to seal it there.
In that case—
However...
Only one with the blood of the royal family might be able to do it—
that is to say, only you.
It's said that in the past, we were able to undo the seal
and bring the Ark here by releasing the king's soul.
If you wish to seal it again, Alexei,
I have no idea what will become of you.
Is sealing the Ark the right choice even if it means exposing yourself to danger?
Consider that question well.
Daddy!
Dad!
If that will let them live with the new pride of the Sirius in their hearts...
I'll come back as soon as the Ark is sealed.
If you take too long, Yuliy will forget you, understand?
Well, we can't have that.
You won't forget me, will you?
Of course not.
Sachi.
I'm sorry.
You're so strange sometimes.
Why are you apologizing?
Don't you mean, "I'll see you later"?
Yeah, you're right.
Dad!
Yuliy.
Dad?
Is that everything you wanted to know?
You know what happened now.
If that's all you wanted, then go on home.
Wait!
Are you...
Are you going to be like this forever, Dad?
Sealing the Ark means releasing the soul of its protector.
My soul exists alongside the seal.
You understand what that implies, right?
But that means you'll be left with this tragedy forever!
After you left the village, Dogville was attacked by vampires seeking the Ark.
Mom, Gustav, and everyone else died.
Mikhail risked his life to protect me,
but he became a vampire as a result.
You sacrificed your life for the sake of our happiness—for the sake of the Sirius' future—
and then...
How can I live with something this cruel?
So that's why you called this a tragedy?
Much has been sacrificed,
but this seal is protecting the peace of the world.
Its present and future peace both.
"No matter what hardships befall us,
the Sirius will live here with the Ark."
If shackling me to that old tradition will let the Sirius part ways with it, then so be it.
As your father, I don't want these shackles to ever bind you.
Please understand, Yuliy.
No, Dad.
That can't be right.
You didn't make a mistake,
but it's fundamentally the same thing!
As she lay dying, Mom said "live" to me!
I understand what she meant now!
She wanted me to live and complete what you wanted to accomplish!
Yuliy...
It's wrong that anyone should ever have to be a sacrifice for the sake of someone else's happiness!
So I...
I want to find a way other than sealing the Ark.
I'm going to live.
I'll live in order to prove that the the new pride of the Sirius that you showed us was the right one!
To think that the day would come that I'd get preached to by little Yuliy.
It's thanks to Mom and Mikhail.
Mom taught me your stature,
and Mikhail taught me your strength.
They raised me and passed your will on together.
Did they, now.
Yuliy.
You just might be able to do what I couldn't.
Dad...
Take it.
I'll be watching over you with Mom as you find your answer.
Dad!
The hell?
What's going on?
It's starting, it's starting!
It's finally happened.
I've been waiting for you,
Ark of the Sirius!
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
I need to settle the score myself.
Give me the Ark!
Wake up, Brother!
All we needed was for you to stay out of here!
You bastard!